<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Books on Read in English</title>
    <link>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/book/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Books on Read in English</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>pt-br</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/book/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A Blessed Blunder</title>
      <link>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/a-blessed-blunder/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/a-blessed-blunder/</guid>
      <description>A Blessed Blunder At a gospel meeting in Des Moines I had preached as clearly as I could the glorious Word of the Christ of the cross. Afterward, noticing a young man trying to avoid me, I went straight over to him.
After a brief conversation I persuaded him to come with me into a small adjoining room. I learned that it was through a “mistake” that he had “blundered” into the meeting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Changed Life</title>
      <link>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/a-changed-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/a-changed-life/</guid>
      <description>A Changed Life That which occurred seemed like a nightmare, but it was not. Once I was a healthy and strong man; but I became disabled. Another transformation was about to take place in a way I never would have imagined.
It was August 8, 1987 when I had a drastic change in my life. I was passing by a bar and decided to go in for a drink. I was not aware that there was a man inside who wanted to kill me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Daring Challenge</title>
      <link>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/a-daring-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/a-daring-challenge/</guid>
      <description>A Daring Challenge There lived in Germany years ago a countess of the House of Hanover. She was a noted unbeliever, especially opposed to the teaching of resurrection and eternal life.
This descendant of royalty died when about thirty years old. Before she passed away she gave written orders that her grave should be covered with a solid granite slab; that around it should be fitted square blocks of stone; and that the corners should be fastened to each other and to the granite slab by heavy iron clamps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Home Higher than Mountains</title>
      <link>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/a-home-higher-than-mountains/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/a-home-higher-than-mountains/</guid>
      <description>A Home Higher than Mountains It was New Year&amp;#039;s Day when the drums and flutes began to play. Now, three days later, the drums continued to boom out their rhythms and the flutes kept playing their short, shrill tunes over and over. Men and women from a town high in the Andes Mountains had been dancing up and dawn the streets for all three days. They were so tired that they could hardly keep on dancing, but still they did not stop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Man of His Word</title>
      <link>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/a-man-of-his-word/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/a-man-of-his-word/</guid>
      <description>A Man of His Word During the French-English war years ago, an English general was planning an attack. He ordered the officer whose duty it was to provide the troops with food to have the rations ready and at a certain place named by him at twelve o’clock on the following day.
It was sometimes difficult to provide sufficient supplies; and the officer replied that the rations could not be at the place on such short notice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A True Shark Story</title>
      <link>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/a-true-shark-story/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/a-true-shark-story/</guid>
      <description>A True Shark Story
In that playful marine acrobat, the porpoise, the shark has an enemy that will permit no intrusion on its feeding grounds. This fact came out in the course of a story told about themselves by two old and experienced Christian fishermen while conducting a fishing excursion off Swan Beach, New Jersey, many years ago. The story which appeared first in Harper’s Weekly was as follows: “Some ten years ago we were hard drinkers, swearers, wild surfmen and fishermen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Valiant Captain</title>
      <link>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/a-valiant-captain/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/a-valiant-captain/</guid>
      <description>A Valiant Captain A Valiant Captain’s Effort
The “Patrick Morris” was a large ferry boat which carried passengers and cars across the strait between Nova Scotia and Newfoundland. The captain was justly proud of his boat which had made the trip safely many times.
One day while the ferry was in the harbor at Port aux Basques, a violent storm came up. The waves in the strait rolled high as the wind blew harder and harder.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A stealthy attack from a hidden enemy</title>
      <link>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/a-stealthy-attack-from-a-hidden-enemy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/a-stealthy-attack-from-a-hidden-enemy/</guid>
      <description>A stealthy attack from a hidden enemy When I was in junior high school, my uncle invited me and some of my friends over to his house for supper. For dessert, among other things, was a plate of figs. Yum! Figs and dates and raisins are my favorite dried fruits. They come originally from mid-east countries like Israel, Egypt, Lebanon, Syria, among others.
While we were eating the figs, one of the boys said to my uncle, &amp;quot;We&amp;#039;ve been studying about bacteria at school.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Irish Soldier’s Sacrifice</title>
      <link>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/an-irish-soldier-s-sacrifice/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/an-irish-soldier-s-sacrifice/</guid>
      <description>An Irish Soldier’s Sacrifice In a cemetery on the Aisne River, in France, is the grave of a soldier. It is marked only by a simple cross, with no name; but it has upon it an inscription that arrests the attention of the passer-by.
During World War 1, this unknown soldier was a private of the Royal Irish Guards. A corporal of the West Yorkshire Regiment, who was in a hospital at Woolrich, told the story of the unknown hero who was buried with full military honors, his fellow-soldiers erecting the cross over his grave, and inscribing upon it the words—”He saved others; himself he could not save.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anchored</title>
      <link>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/anchored/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/anchored/</guid>
      <description>Anchored The 16,000 ton tanker “British Sportsman” was berthed at an oil dock in Antwerp, Belgium. Her cargo, three million gallons of crude oil from Kuwait on the Persian Gulf, had just been unloaded. Preparatory for her return journey and to make the vessel easier to handle on the high seas, the emptied oil tanks were being filled with water for ballast.
It was miserable weather in late fall. The air was beginning to turn cold and rain was annoyingly frequent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are You Acquainted With the Author</title>
      <link>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/are-you-acquainted-with-the-author/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/are-you-acquainted-with-the-author/</guid>
      <description>Are You Acquainted With the Author “I am personally acquainted with the author.” That was the reply of a Christian when challenged by a skeptic as to the authenticity of the Bible.
There are many who have Bibles but have no personal acquaintance with the Author! How many there are who regard the Bible as merely a masterpiece of English literature, or perhaps go as far as to call it, “The good Book.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arrested by a Song</title>
      <link>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/arrested-by-a-song/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/arrested-by-a-song/</guid>
      <description>Arrested by a Song It was a busy scene at an American railroad station. The train was late and the waiting room crowded.
One loud-voiced man seemed to take pleasure in constantly cursing using the name of Christ, to the intense disgust of many of the passengers. But regardless of the discomfort he caused, the man kept on.
Presently, above the voice of the swearer, rose the beautiful words of a hymn sung in a manly voice:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Between Two Slides</title>
      <link>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/between-two-slides/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/between-two-slides/</guid>
      <description>Between Two Slides Catastrophic snow-slides are not uncommon in the Canadian Rocky Mountains. Suddenly and without warning, massive build-ups of snow take off rapidly down the mountain sides, overcoming or burying everything in their paths. One such slide buried a British Columbia motel and gasoline station, killing several people, in 1974. A short time later a skier died there beneath an avalanche. During one fateful week in March years ago over eight hundred people are said to have died in Rocky Mountain snowstorms and slides.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christ Your Griefs Has Borne</title>
      <link>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/christ-your-griefs-has-borne/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/christ-your-griefs-has-borne/</guid>
      <description>Christ Your Griefs Has Borne Surely Christ your griefs has borne!
Weeping soul no longer mourn:
View Him bleeding on the tree,
Pouring out His life for thee.
Weary sinner, keep your eyes
On the atoning Sacrifice:
There the Lord upon the tree
Numbered with transgressors see.
Cast your guilty soul on Him;
Find Him mighty to redeem;
At His feet your burden lay —
Look your doubts and fears away.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>God’s X-Rays</title>
      <link>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/god-s-x-rays/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/god-s-x-rays/</guid>
      <description>God’s X-Rays God has His spiritual X-rays!
“The Lord looketh on the heart” (1 Samuel 16:7). “His eyes behold, His eyelids try, the children of men” (Psalm 11:4). “Thou understandest my thought afar off” (Psalm 139:2). “I the Lord search the heart, I try the reins” (Jeremiah 17:10).
Would you and I like our inner history to be published or revealed? God’s X-rays reveal all. And if sin is not blotted out by atonement, the “plates” as it were will come up for judgment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>His Last Chance!</title>
      <link>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/his-last-chance/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/his-last-chance/</guid>
      <description>His Last Chance! There was once a poor man who earned his living by gathering eggs along the rocky cliffs. One morning he went out on his dangerous errand and, looking down from the summit, he saw a ledge jutting out from the rock below covered with a cluster of birds’ nests. He fastened his rope to a tree which stood near the edge, and then gradually let himself down to the edge of the rock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>History of &#34;True Stories&#34; Website</title>
      <link>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/historyofsite/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/historyofsite/</guid>
      <description>About Me I was born in 1955, and came to know the Lord Jesus in 1978. You can read the story of my conversion at &amp;quot;When Angels Rejoice&amp;quot;. Since then, I have worked as an architect, an editor, and a translator, and now I work as a consultant, writer and speaker. I write business articles and stories for many sites, newspapers and magazines and give lectures on business and marketing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It’s All on Before</title>
      <link>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/it-s-all-on-before/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/it-s-all-on-before/</guid>
      <description>It’s All on Before I was driving lately with a friend on one of the beautiful side roads in the Great Smokies of North Carolina. We came to a gate across the road, put there to prevent cattle from straying away from a piece of pasture land close by. When we were getting near the gate, my friend told me that a young man would be there to open it for us, and added: “Say a word to him about the Lord.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jesus Loves Me</title>
      <link>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/jesus-loves-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/jesus-loves-me/</guid>
      <description>Jesus Loves Me Often a long-forgotten sacred song learned in childhood is recalled years later and used of God to bring a lost soul to Christ. Little is much when God is in it! The mighty power of the simple truth contained in Anna B. Warner’s “Jesus loves me,” is shown in the following true story— the personally related experience of “a woman that was a sinner.”
She told it to the preacher following a gospel meeting during which he had noted the rapt attention of the woman unknown to him, and heard her irrepressible “Amen!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Last Chance</title>
      <link>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/my-last-chance/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/my-last-chance/</guid>
      <description>My Last Chance One June day in 1969 the USS Constellation lay out in the Pacific Ocean about 200 miles off the coast of San Diego. Two flight crewmen went out on the flight deck to saddle up on their F-4 twin-engine two-place fighter bomber. They climbed into the aircraft and turned it on; the huffer came up and blew hot air through the turbines as the raw fuel was poured in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Never Perish</title>
      <link>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/never-perish/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/never-perish/</guid>
      <description>Never Perish “My sheep… shall never perish” (John 10:27-28). These are the words of Jesus, the Son of God. He is the Good Shepherd who gave His life for the sheep; and now risen, He gives His own eternal life to the sheep. His own pledge is, “They shall never perish.”
No, He does not say, They shall never wander; He does not say, They shall never backslide; He does not say, They shall never stumble, but He does say, “They shall never PERISH.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New York World Trade Center Under Attack</title>
      <link>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/new-york-world-trade-center-under-attack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/new-york-world-trade-center-under-attack/</guid>
      <description>New York World Trade Center Under Attack! Tuesday, September 11, 2001. It is 8:45 a.m. in New York City. The morning sun hits the twin towers of World Trade Center, where thousands of people are working. Suddenly American Airlines Flight 11 Boeing 767, hijacked by terrorists, slams into the north tower of the World Trade Center. The airplane was en route from Boston&amp;#039;s Logan Airport to Los Angeles International with 92 people onboard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ready for The Race</title>
      <link>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/ready-for-the-race/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/ready-for-the-race/</guid>
      <description>Ready for The Race In the late afternoon of October 30, 1987, just after I had become 19, there were many young people in my snack bar. Until that afternoon, I had been a normally healthy young man. My life existed in entertainment, partying, games and girls. I thought my life would not have any meaning without pleasure and entertainment; so I had no concern about my future. But the future about which I had given no thought was about to have a tragic beginning for me that day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ready to Die</title>
      <link>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/ready-to-die/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/ready-to-die/</guid>
      <description>Ready to Die The gunmen asked for &amp;quot;those who believe in God&amp;quot; to stand up. Then the killer pointed his gun at Cassie Bernall and asked her the life-or-death question: &amp;quot;Do you believe in Jesus?&amp;quot; After a long hesitation, she looked to the young man, and said: &amp;quot;Yes, I love Jesus&amp;quot;. That was the last thing this 17-year-old Christian would ever say. The gunman asked her &amp;quot;Why?&amp;quot; She had no time to answer before she was shot to death.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Romans 1:1</title>
      <link>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/romans-1-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/romans-1-1/</guid>
      <description>Romans 1:1 says, “Paul, a servant of Jesus Christ,
called to be an apostle,
separated unto the gospel of God.”
We are all servants or slaves of God or servants of our own lusts and desires. People love to think of themselves as free, bold agents of change. Apple used to encourage us to Think Different. Paul boldly says he’s a “servant” or “slave” of Jesus Christ.
But Paul was called to be the unique Apostle to the Gentiles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TSUNAMI - The Picture of a Nightmare</title>
      <link>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/tsunami-the-picture-of-a-nightmare/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/tsunami-the-picture-of-a-nightmare/</guid>
      <description>TSUNAMI - The Picture of a Nightmare December 26 – the day after Christmas – is restful in many parts of the world. Gifts have been opened, relatives visited, special meals eaten. There is nothing left to do but dream of summer. After the holidays, it&amp;#039;s tempting to fantasize about packing bags and flying to exotic beaches with blue waves, palm trees, sun and sand.
So, a resort in Thailand advertises: &amp;quot;Khao Lak Beach – Five-Star Luxury Resort.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Book Seller</title>
      <link>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/the-book-seller/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/the-book-seller/</guid>
      <description>The Book Seller A Christian bookseller was traveling in South America, his mule laden with the precious Scriptures. Night was beginning to fall when he saw in the distance a company of merchants. They had stopped to camp for the night. The bookseller approached them and asked if he might camp with them. They readily agreed and invited him to share their evening meal by the fire.
As they sat around the cheerful blaze after their simple supper, the Christian took a Bible from his pocket and asked permission to read to them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Jailbird&#39;s Song</title>
      <link>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/the-jailbird-s-song/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/the-jailbird-s-song/</guid>
      <description>The Jailbird&amp;#039;s Song On January 7, 1993 I was a broken man &amp;ndash; lost, hurt, angry, and confused. Locked in jail, my life already destroyed through drugs and crime, I had just received shattering news. The mother of my two youngest children had been murdered, stabbed to death by a male acquaintance and neighbor. Overwhelmed with grief and fear for my children, I, a hardened 41-year-old convict, stood sobbing for hours in front of everyone in the cellblock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Stairs</title>
      <link>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/the-stairs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/the-stairs/</guid>
      <description>The Stairs When I was growing up, we lived in a little house with a full basement. Mom made the basement cozy with a rug covering the concrete floor and a couch and chair that we could play on. My brothers and I played down there a lot, and that was where we kept most of our toys and the things we treasured.
We went up and down those wooden stairs many times, and after a while they began to look pretty scuffed and scruffy.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>