<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Books on Read in English</title>
    <link>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/book/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Books on Read in English</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>pt-br</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/book/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A Home Higher than Mountains</title>
      <link>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/a-home-higher-than-mountains/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/a-home-higher-than-mountains/</guid>
      <description>A Home Higher than Mountains It was New Year&amp;#039;s Day when the drums and flutes began to play. Now, three days later, the drums continued to boom out their rhythms and the flutes kept playing their short, shrill tunes over and over. Men and women from a town high in the Andes Mountains had been dancing up and dawn the streets for all three days. They were so tired that they could hardly keep on dancing, but still they did not stop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A stealthy attack from a hidden enemy</title>
      <link>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/a-stealthy-attack-from-a-hidden-enemy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/a-stealthy-attack-from-a-hidden-enemy/</guid>
      <description>A stealthy attack from a hidden enemy
When I was in junior high school, my uncle invited me and some of my friends over to his house for supper. For dessert, among other things, was a plate of figs. Yum! Figs and dates and raisins are my favorite dried fruits. They come originally from mid-east countries like Israel, Egypt, Lebanon, Syria, among others.
While we were eating the figs, one of the boys said to my uncle, &amp;quot;We&amp;#039;ve been studying about bacteria at school.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>His Last Chance!</title>
      <link>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/his-last-chance/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/his-last-chance/</guid>
      <description>His Last Chance! There was once a poor man who earned his living by gathering eggs along the rocky cliffs. One morning he went out on his dangerous errand and, looking down from the summit, he saw a ledge jutting out from the rock below covered with a cluster of birds’ nests. He fastened his rope to a tree which stood near the edge, and then gradually let himself down to the edge of the rock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>History of &#34;True Stories&#34; Website</title>
      <link>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/historyofsite/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/historyofsite/</guid>
      <description>About Me I was born in 1955, and came to know the Lord Jesus in 1978. You can read the story of my conversion at &amp;quot;When Angels Rejoice&amp;quot;. Since then, I have worked as an architect, an editor, and a translator, and now I work as a consultant, writer and speaker. I write business articles and stories for many sites, newspapers and magazines and give lectures on business and marketing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New York World Trade Center Under Attack</title>
      <link>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/new-york-world-trade-center-under-attack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/new-york-world-trade-center-under-attack/</guid>
      <description>New York World Trade Center Under Attack! Tuesday, September 11, 2001. It is 8:45 a.m. in New York City. The morning sun hits the twin towers of World Trade Center, where thousands of people are working. Suddenly American Airlines Flight 11 Boeing 767, hijacked by terrorists, slams into the north tower of the World Trade Center. The airplane was en route from Boston&amp;#039;s Logan Airport to Los Angeles International with 92 people onboard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ready for The Race</title>
      <link>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/ready-for-the-race/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/ready-for-the-race/</guid>
      <description>Ready for The Race In the late afternoon of October 30, 1987, just after I had become 19, there were many young people in my snack bar. Until that afternoon, I had been a normally healthy young man. My life existed in entertainment, partying, games and girls. I thought my life would not have any meaning without pleasure and entertainment; so I had no concern about my future. But the future about which I had given no thought was about to have a tragic beginning for me that day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ready to Die</title>
      <link>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/ready-to-die/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/ready-to-die/</guid>
      <description>Ready to Die The gunmen asked for &amp;quot;those who believe in God&amp;quot; to stand up. Then the killer pointed his gun at Cassie Bernall and asked her the life-or-death question: &amp;quot;Do you believe in Jesus?&amp;quot; After a long hesitation, she looked to the young man, and said: &amp;quot;Yes, I love Jesus&amp;quot;. That was the last thing this 17-year-old Christian would ever say. The gunman asked her &amp;quot;Why?&amp;quot; She had no time to answer before she was shot to death.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TSUNAMI - The Picture of a Nightmare</title>
      <link>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/tsunami-the-picture-of-a-nightmare/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/tsunami-the-picture-of-a-nightmare/</guid>
      <description>TSUNAMI - The Picture of a Nightmare December 26 – the day after Christmas – is restful in many parts of the world. Gifts have been opened, relatives visited, special meals eaten. There is nothing left to do but dream of summer. After the holidays, it&amp;#039;s tempting to fantasize about packing bags and flying to exotic beaches with blue waves, palm trees, sun and sand.
So, a resort in Thailand advertises: &amp;quot;Khao Lak Beach – Five-Star Luxury Resort.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Jailbird&#39;s Song</title>
      <link>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/the-jailbird-s-song/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/the-jailbird-s-song/</guid>
      <description>The Jailbird&amp;#039;s Song On January 7, 1993 I was a broken man &amp;ndash; lost, hurt, angry, and confused. Locked in jail, my life already destroyed through drugs and crime, I had just received shattering news. The mother of my two youngest children had been murdered, stabbed to death by a male acquaintance and neighbor. Overwhelmed with grief and fear for my children, I, a hardened 41-year-old convict, stood sobbing for hours in front of everyone in the cellblock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Stairs</title>
      <link>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/the-stairs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/the-stairs/</guid>
      <description>The Stairs
When I was growing up, we lived in a little house with a full basement. Mom made the basement cozy with a rug covering the concrete floor and a couch and chair that we could play on. My brothers and I played down there a lot, and that was where we kept most of our toys and the things we treasured.
We went up and down those wooden stairs many times, and after a while they began to look pretty scuffed and scruffy.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>