<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Books on Read in English</title>
    <link>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/book/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Books on Read in English</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>pt-br</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/book/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>History of &#34;True Stories&#34; Website</title>
      <link>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/historyofsite/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/historyofsite/</guid>
      <description>About Me I was born in 1955, and came to know the Lord Jesus in 1978. You can read the story of my conversion at &amp;quot;When Angels Rejoice&amp;quot;. Since then, I have worked as an architect, an editor, and a translator, and now I work as a consultant, writer and speaker. I write business articles and stories for many sites, newspapers and magazines and give lectures on business and marketing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ready for The Race</title>
      <link>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/ready-for-the-race/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/ready-for-the-race/</guid>
      <description>Ready for The Race In the late afternoon of October 30, 1987, just after I had become 19, there were many young people in my snack bar. Until that afternoon, I had been a normally healthy young man. My life existed in entertainment, partying, games and girls. I thought my life would not have any meaning without pleasure and entertainment; so I had no concern about my future. But the future about which I had given no thought was about to have a tragic beginning for me that day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ready to Die</title>
      <link>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/ready-to-die/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/ready-to-die/</guid>
      <description>Ready to Die The gunmen asked for &amp;quot;those who believe in God&amp;quot; to stand up. Then the killer pointed his gun at Cassie Bernall and asked her the life-or-death question: &amp;quot;Do you believe in Jesus?&amp;quot; After a long hesitation, she looked to the young man, and said: &amp;quot;Yes, I love Jesus&amp;quot;. That was the last thing this 17-year-old Christian would ever say. The gunman asked her &amp;quot;Why?&amp;quot; She had no time to answer before she was shot to death.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Jailbird&#39;s Song</title>
      <link>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/the-jailbird-s-song/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leituracrista.com/app/readinenglish/the-jailbird-s-song/</guid>
      <description>The Jailbird&amp;#039;s Song On January 7, 1993 I was a broken man &amp;ndash; lost, hurt, angry, and confused. Locked in jail, my life already destroyed through drugs and crime, I had just received shattering news. The mother of my two youngest children had been murdered, stabbed to death by a male acquaintance and neighbor. Overwhelmed with grief and fear for my children, I, a hardened 41-year-old convict, stood sobbing for hours in front of everyone in the cellblock.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>